nupark.com 2018-12-10

# Privacy Policy

NuPark, LLC (“NuPark” or “We”) maintains its Web site (“Site”) as a parking management system for our client operator (pages containing www.nupark.com or www.nuparkonline.com ). The security of your personal information is extremely important to us. We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We're committed to protecting the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us, and we'll only use that information as described below.

## DISCLAIMER

NuPark maintains its web sites on an on-going basis, but it does not represent, guarantee, or warrant that all information provided is accurate, complete, current, or suitable for the viewer's purposes. NuPark specifically disclaims any and all liability for claims or damages that may result from its Web sites or information contained therein, including any Web sites maintained by third parties and linked to NuPark Web sites, for which responsibility lies with the entity providing the information. A link from NuPark Web sites in no way implies endorsement of that site by NuPark.

## COOKIES

NuPark may use cookies to track the date of last visit to a specific page or to identify a session at a particular Web site. (Note: A cookie file contains unique information a Web site can use to track things like passwords, and lists of pages or Web sites visited.)

## SERVER LOGS

NuPark uses Log analysis tools to create summary statistics, which are used for purposes such as assessing what information is of most interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. The following information may be collected for this analysis including, but not limited to:

  * User Client hostname - The hostname (or IP address if DNS is disabled) of the user/client requesting access
  * HTTP header, "user-agent" - The user-agent information includes the type of browser, its version, and the operating system it is running on
  * HTTP header, "referrer" - The referrer specifies the page from which the client accessed the current page
  * System date - The date and time of the user/client request
  * Full request - The exact request the user/client made
  * Status - The status code the server returned to the user/client
  * Content length - The content length, in bytes, of the document sent to the user/client
  * Method - The request method used
  * Universal Resource Identifier (URI) - The location of a resource on the server
  * Query string of the URI - Anything after the question mark in a URI
  * Protocol - The transport protocol and version used

### PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

What Personal Information We Collect We collect personal information that you provide when using the Site. This information includes your first and last name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, identification numbers, vehicle descriptions and license plate number(s). You can browse this Site without creating an account, but you will need to create an account when you pay for citations or permits or when you appeal a citation and in order to take advantage of certain features. We may ask you to confirm your personal information when you contact us. This will allow us to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity.

### Purchase Information

When you make a transaction with NuPark, we collect your name, IP address and payment method information, such as credit card confirmation. We collect this information in order to record your payment on your account. We also collect information that allows the parking operator to ship your permit. This includes the name, address, and phone number. None of your sensitive credit card information is processed or stored in our system. The credit card transaction is done with Authorize.net, an industry-leading third-party payment processor. Only the confirmation information regarding the payment is received back into our system, such as payment amount and confirmation number.

If you send us an electronic mail message with a question or comment that contains personally identifying information, or fill out a form that e-mails us this information, we will only use the personally-identifiable information to respond to your request and analyze trends. We may redirect your message to our client parking operator who is in a better position to answer your question. For site management functions, information is collected for analysis and statistical purposes. This information is not reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information and will not be released to any outside parties unless legally required to do so in connection with law enforcement investigations or other legal proceedings.

## SECURITY MEASURES

Some of the information contained on the Web Servers is private information intended for specific individuals or departments. This may include accounting information, personnel information, or other items of a sensitive nature. This information is protected by passwords assigned to each individual who has need to access it. Unauthorized persons are not able to access any of this private information. We want you to feel completely secure when conducting business with us on line. We use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which encrypts (or encodes) sensitive information using 128-bit encryption algorithms provided by RSA Security before it is sent over the Internet.

## LINKS

This Web site contains links to other sites, and NuPark is not responsible for privacy policies on those sites. Questions about this privacy policy may be directed to the respective Webmaster for each site: www.nupark.com, www.nuparkonline.com If you do not agree to (or cannot comply with) any of the site Terms of Use, do not use this Site. This Privacy Policy was last updated on October 19, 2014. We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time. Please check our Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Use of this Site after modification implies that you consent to this Privacy Policy as modified.

## REFUNDS AND DISPUTED CHARGES

If you need to request a refund or dispute a payment, please contact our client operator directly.
